Carmen McRae Collection of Musical Arrangements and Other Materials
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1931-1976 (Box 1-40)
  - It could happen to you, Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #116 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - It doesn't matter, John Wallowitch / Tony Scibetta; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 12/6)
  - It isn't a secret, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/7)
  - It might as well be Spring, Richard Rodgers / Oscar Hammerstein II; Parts (guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #427 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - It never entered my mind, Guitar part; Small group #139 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - It shouldn't happen to a dream, Score and parts (production, vocal, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, horn 1-4, bass trombone, tuba, woodwinds 1-4, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #178 (Box-folder 39/5)
  - It takes a man, Mildred Mayne; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/10)
  - It takes a whole lot of human feeling, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 12/11)
  - It was great while it lasted, Jerry Goldstone / Johnny Rotella; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/12)
  - It will only hurt a minute, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/13)
  - It won't bother me, Ronnell L. Bright; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/14)
  - It's a beautiful night, Joáo Donato / Mercedes Chies; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/15)
  - It's a relief (now that it's over), Hal Blair / Dean Kays; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/16)
  - It's down the hill all the way to my house, Robert Wells / Cy Coleman; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/17)
  - It's easy to remember, Lyric sheet (Box-folder 12/18)
  - It's great to be alive, Parts (booth, vocal); Arranged by Benny Carter (Box-folder 12/19)
  - It's like love, Caryl Young / Jean Galvis; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/20)
  - It's love, Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Ernie Wilkins; Small group #100 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - It's not going that way, John Keating / Johnny Worth; Score and parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #343 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - It's not time for you to go, D.I. Andreas; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/23)
  - It's time we met, Tom Garvin; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/24)
  - I've waited for a waltz, Johnny Mercer / Johnny Rotella; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Jo Sullivan [medley], Score, vocal lead sheet; Titles: Don't cry; I like everybody; Warm all over; "Something wonderful" recording - salute to women of Broadway (Box-folder 38/5)
  - Judy Holliday [medley], Score, vocal lead sheet; Titles: Long before I knew you; Just in time; "Something wonderful" recording - salute to women of Broadway (Box-folder 38/6)
  - Just a dream ago, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, double bass, drums) (missing guitar, piano); Arranged by Jimmy Jones; Small group #389 (Box-folder 30/1)
  - Just a gigolo, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #225 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Just a little lovin', Score and parts (horn, flute, alto saxophone, oboe, bassoon, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion); Arranged by Arif Mardin; Small group # 395 (Box-folder 35/4)
  - Just another Monday, Fred Taggart, Jr.; Lyric sheet (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Just friends, John Klenner / Sam M. Lewis; Lyric sheet (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Just give me time, Francy Boland / Jimmy Woode; Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone 1-3, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Francy Boland (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Just in time, Score and parts (conductor, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #271 (Box-folder 35/5)
  - Just one of those things, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #14 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Just sitting here, Charles Lazar; Lead sheet (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Just you - just me, Lead sheet (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Kick off your shoes, Parts (guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #190 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Kind of Bill (A tribute to Bill Evans), Joe La Barbera / Ralph Sharon; Lead sheet; Cassette recording transferred to The Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division (MBRS) at the Library of Congress. (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Kiss me awake every morning, rock me awake every night, Ronnell L. Bright / Tommy Wolf; Lyric sheet (Box-folder 13/10)
  - The lady is a tramp, Score and parts (conductor, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #106 (Box-folder 35/6)
  - Land of make believe, Chuck Mangione; Printed sketch for score (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Last night, Score and parts (vocal, conductor, trumpet, flute, clarinet 1-2, oboe, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Ralph Burns; Small group #69 (Box-folder 30/2)
  - Last night when we were young, Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 13/12)
  - Late last night, Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Laugh? I though I'd die, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Laughing boy, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass); Small group #77 (Box-folder 13/15)
  - A letter for Anna Lee, Parts (vocal, master rhythm); Arranged by Dave Grusin (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Let's call it a day, Lew Brown / Ray Henderson; Double bass part; Small group #157 (Box-folder 13/17)
  - Life is just a bowl of cherries, Score and parts (production, vocal, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, horn 1-4, tuba, flute 1-3, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone 1-2, bassoon, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion 1-2); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #174 (Box-folder 40/1)
  - Life's a mockingbird, Parts (vocal, double bass) (Box-folder 13/18)
  - Limehouse blues, Score and parts (vocal, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, horn 1-4, tuba, flute 1-2, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone 1-2, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion 1-2); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #176 (Box-folder 40/2)
  - Limehouse blues, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #176 (Box-folder 13/19)
  - Linger awhile, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Tom Garvin (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Linger awhile, Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 13/20)
  - A little bit more, Lead sheet (Box-folder 13/21)
  - Little green apples, Score, sheet music and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Jimmy Jones (Box-folder 30/3)
  - Little Niles, Randy Weston; Lead sheet (no lyrics) (Box-folder 13/22)
  - A little taste, Dave Frishberg / Johnny Hodges; Lead sheet (Box-folder 13/23)
  - A little tear, Eumir Deodato / Ray Gilbert; Lead sheet (Box-folder 13/24)
  - Live at Birdland West, Performance/solo cue sheets; Titles: Black and blue; Cherokee; Fine and mellow; Just friends; Long ago and far away; My handyman ain't handy no more; One more chance; These foolish things remind me of you; Until the real thing comes along; Personell: Carmen McRae; Red Holloway (tenor, alto saxophone); Jack McDuff (organ); Phil Upchurch (guitar); John Clayton (bass); Paul Humphrey (drums) (Box-folder 13/25)
  - Live for life, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #200 (Box-folder 13/26)
  - Livin', Tom Garvin; Lead sheet; piano part (Box-folder 13/27)
  - Lo and behold, C. Singleton / R. Simon / M. Lewis; Score and parts (trumpet 1-2, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar); Small gropup #135 (Box-folder 30/4)
  - Loads of love, Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Oliver Nelson (Box-folder 13/28)
  - Loads of love, Parts (guitar, drums); Small group #194 (Box-folder 13/29)
  - Lonely little people, Tony Scibetta / John Wallowitch; Piano-vocal score; Small group #77 (Box-folder 13/30)
  - Long before I knew you, Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #259 (Box-folder 13/31)
  - Lonliness, Paul Williams / Ken Ascher; Lead sheet and parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 13/32)
  - Look at me, Jean Galvis / Caryl Young; Lead sheet (Box-folder 13/33)
  - Look at that face, Guitar part; Small group #319 (Box-folder 13/34)
  - Look for love, Gene DiNovi / Dick Gautier; Lead sheet; Laid in: note from Gene DiNovi (Box-folder 13/35)
  - The look of love, Burt Bacharach / Hal David; Score and parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, woodwinds 1-4, piano/conductor, guitar/double bass, drums, percussion 1-2); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #351 (Box-folder 40/3)
  - The look of love, Burt Bacharach / Hal David; Score and parts (vocallead, trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #351 (Box-folder 30/5)
  - Look to the children, Chuck Mangione; Printed sketch for score (Box-folder 13/36)
  - Los Angeles, Monique Aldebert / Louis Aldebert; Lead sheet and parts (guitar, double bass) (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Lost up in loving you, William Smith / Kenny Rankin / Yvonne Rankin; Lead sheet; Arranged by Dave Grusin (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Love came on stealthy fingers, Bob Dorough; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Love in vain, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #45 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Love is a night time thing, Bob Haymes; Score and parts (production, vocal, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, horn 1-4, tuba, woodwinds 1-4, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion 1-2); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #170 (Box-folder 40/4)
  - Love is a storm, Bill Rubenstein / Carmen Huesman / Rick Huesman; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Love is confusion, Christine Gardner; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Love is here, Piano part; Small group #4 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Love is like the sea, Gene DiNovi / By Dunham; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Love light, Orlando Murden; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Love me by name, Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Love me or leave me, Lyric sheet (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Lover man, Piano part; Small group #1 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Lover's caravan, Richard Ahlert / Marvin Fisher; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Lush invitation, Bobby Enriquez / Jon Hendricks; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Lush life, Billy Strayhorn; Score and parts (vocal, horn, flute, clarinet 1-2, bass clarinet, harp, guitar, drums) (missing piano, double bass) (Box-folder 30/6)
  - MacArthur Park, Jimmy Webb; Parts (vocal, double bass, drums); Small group #375 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Mad about the boy, Noel Coward; Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group # 131 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - Make someone happy, Double bass part; Small group #255 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Make you laugh, Guitar part; Small group #35 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - The man from yesterday, Margo Guryan; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/19)
  - The man I love, Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, tuba, English horn, horn, flute 1-3, clarinet 1-3, bass clarinet, oboe 1-3, bassoon 1-3, contra bassoon, celeste, piano/conductor, rhythm score, percussion, strings); Arranged by Bill Holman (Box-folder 14/20)
  - Mary Martin [medley], Score, vocal lead sheet; Titles: A cock-eyed optimist; Wonderful guy; "Something wonderful" recording - salute to women of Broadway (Box-folder 38/8)
  - Masquerade, Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 14/21)
  - Meaning of the blues, Guitar part; Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #257 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - Medley, Guitar part; Titles: Days of wine and roses; It's impossible (Box-folder 14/23)
  - Medley: I wanna be around / You're nobody 'til somebody love you, Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 36/1)
  - Meet me half way, Leonard Feather / Dory Langdon; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/24)
  - Melancholy mood, Bernice Ross / Marian McPartland; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/25)
  - Melanctha, Dave Brubeck / Liz Blake; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 14/26)
  - Melanctha see Brubeck folder, Dave Brubeck; Lyric sheet
  - Milano, John Lewis; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/27)
  - A mind is a terrible thing to waste (jingle), Lead sheet (no lyrics) (Box-folder 14/28)
  - Misery loves company, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 14/29)
  - Miss Brown, Guitar part; Small group #134 (Box-folder 14/30)
  - Miss Brown to you, Leo Robin / Richard Whiting / Ralph Rainger; Parts (trumpet 1-5, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by John Clayton (Box-folder 14/31)
  - Moanin' low - Libby Holman, Score, vocal lead sheet; "Something wonderful" recording - salute to women of Broadway (Box-folder 38/7)
  - Modesty, Score and parts (horn 1-3, harp, organ, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Don Sebesky (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Monk's dream, Thelonious Monk; Lead sheet (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Moody, Charles DeForest; Lead sheet (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Moon light, Piano part; Small group #142 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - The more I see you, Harry Warren / Mack Gordon; Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxohone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Jimmy Jones (Box-folder 15/4)
  - The more I see you, Harry Warren / Mack Gordon; Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Luther Henderson; Small group #191 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - The more I see you, Harry Warren / Mack Gordon; Parts (guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #391 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - More today than yesterday, Score for trio, parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce; Small group #397 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - More today than yesterday, Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone); Arranged by Arif Mardin; Missing rhythm parts (Box-folder 36/3)
  - The morning after, Margo Guryan; Lead sheet (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Morning star, Lead sheet and parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Motherless child, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass) (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Movin' on, Bob Florence / Johnny Rotella; Lead sheet (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Mr. Magic, Ralph MacDonald / William Salter; Parts (rhythm lead/bass) (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Mr. Meadowlark, Score and parts (vocal, trumpet, horn 1-4, tenor saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Ralph Burns (Box-folder 30/7)
  - Mr. Smith, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #42 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Mr. Ugly, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Francy Boland (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Music, Parts (vocal, piano, lead sheets); Arranged by Dale Oehler (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Music that makes me dance, Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Music that makes me dance, Score and parts (production, vocal, trumpet, horn, woodwinds 1-2, harp, guitar, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Peter Matz (Box-folder 31/1)
  - My future, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #33 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - My kinda world, Score, lead sheet and parts (vocal, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone 1-3, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Francy Boland (Box-folder 15/18)
  - My man, Parts (guitar, double bass); Small group #239 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - My old flame, Piano part (Box-folder 16/2)
  - My one bad habit is falling in love, Dave Brubeck; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/3)
  - My reverie, Larry Clinton; Score and parts (vocal, horn 1-2, trombone 1-4, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Don Sebesky (Box-folder 31/2)
  - My shining hour, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce; Small group #387 (Box-folder 36/4)
  - My shining hour, Lead sheet (no lyrics); Inscribed: Short version; Small group #388 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - My ship, Kurt Weill / Ira Gershwin; Sheet music; guitar part; Small group #229 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - My time is now, Mildred Mayne; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/6)
  - My very own person, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Gene DiNovi; Small group #212 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Mystery, Larry Ford / Mike Campbell; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Necessary evil, Marvin Fisher / Jack Segal; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Never let me go, Guitar part; Small group #220 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Never mind the rain, Bobby Enriquez / Jon Hendricks; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Never say yes, Nat Adderley / Carolyn Plummer; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Never will I marry, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #158 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - New at the game, Shel Feldner / R.C. Jones; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/14)
  - A new day, a new life, a new love, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/15)
  - New York state of mind, Billy Joel; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Nice girls don't stay for breakfast, Jerry Leshay / Bobby Troup; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Nice work, Piano part (Box-folder 16/18)
  - The night has a thousand eyes, Parts (vocal, horn 1-2, trombone 1-4, harp, guitar, percussion, strings); Arranged by Peter Matz (Box-folder 16/19)
  - The night we called it a day [Call it a day], Lyric sheet and parts (piano, guitar, cello, marimba, vibes, cleleste); Small group #157 (Box-folder 16/20)
  - Nite time thing, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #170 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - No more blues, Guitar part; Small group #222 (Box-folder 16/22)
  - No tomorrow, Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/23)
  - Nobody taught me, Leonard Feather; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Not going that way, Conductor score; auxilary trombone part (Box-folder 16/25)
  - Nothing but the best, Johnny Rotella; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 16/26)
  - Nothing like a true love, Della Reese; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/27)
  - Nothing to laugh about, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/28)
  - November girl, Francy Boland; Score, piano-vocal score, drum part (Box-folder 16/29)
  - Now that you're over me, Stacey Dietz; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/30)
  - Nowhere, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #36 (Box-folder 16/31)
  - Nowhere now, Bobby Laurel; Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/32)
  - October lady, Lyric sheet (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Ode to a cowboy see Brubeck folder, Dave Brubeck; Lyric sheet
  - Oh my darling, Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Oh so blue, Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Oh! what a night for love, Neal Hefti / Steve Allen; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Old guitaron, Laurindo Almeida / Johnny Mercer; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/5)
  - On a clear day, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 36/5)
  - On a clear day, Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons (Box-folder 31/3)
  - On a clear day, Parts (piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #192 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - On Green Dolphin Street, Bronisław Kaper; Piano part (Box-folder 17/7)
  - On this day, Carol Coleman Novak / Julian Frazin; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Once upon a Summertime, Score and parts (vocal, horn 1-2, trombone 1-4, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Peter Matz (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Once upon a time, Charles Strouse/ Lee Adams; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Once you're been in love, Michel Legrand / Marilyn Bergman / Alan Bergman; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/10)
  - One day, Margo Guryan; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/11)
  - One drop of rain, Richard Ahlert / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/12)
  - One moment worth years, Lyric sheet (Box-folder 17/13)
  - Only women bleed, Alice Cooper / Dick Wagner; Score; sheet music; parts (guitar, double bass, drums, synthesizer, strings); Arranged by Dave Grusin (Box-folder 17/14)
  - Open your eyes you can fly, Chick Corea / Neville Potter; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/15)
  - Our song, Score; Arranged by Johnny Keating (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Out of the past, Benny Golson / John Hendricks; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/16)
  - The pad next door, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/17)
  - Part time lady, C. Gardner; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/18)
  - The party's over, Jule Styne / Betty Comden / Adolph Green; Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #85 (Box-folder 17/19)
  - Peel me a grape, Dave Frishberg; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/20)
  - Pendulum, Norman Simmons; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 17/21)
  - People, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #309 (Box-folder 17/20)
  - People, places and things, Carroll Coates; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/21)
  - Play it momma, Mary Lou Williams / Gracie Glassman; Lyric sheet (Box-folder 17/22)
  - Play melancholy baby, John Wallowitch / Tony Scibetta; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/23)
  - Playgirl, Dave Newburge / Mike Corda; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/24)
  - Please be kind, Score, conductor score, vocal part (Box-folder 17/25)
  - Please belong to me, Parts (vocal, piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 17/26)
  - Poor butterfly, Raymond Hubbell / John L. Golden; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 17/27)
  - Poor little rich girl, Score and parts (trumpet, flute 1-2, clarinet, bass clarinet, guitar 1-2, piano, double bass, drums); Small group #60 (Box-folder 31/5)
  - A portrait of Duke, M. H. Raskin / Marjorie York / Leonard Feather; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/28)
  - Precious to me, Ronnell Bright; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/29)
  - A premonition of you, Gigi Gryce / John Hendricks; Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/30)
  - Que pasa?, Horace Silver / Fred Bouchard (lyrics); Lyric sheet (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Quiet nights [Corcovado}, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #313 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Quiet now, Danny Zeitlin / Fred Bouchard (lyrics); Lyric sheet (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Quietly there, Morgan Ames / Johnny Mandel; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Raisins in the Sun, Neville B. Lake / Fletcher Smith; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Reflections, Thelonious Monk; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Reminiscing, Gigi Gryce / John Hendricks; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/7)
  - The right to love, Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #377 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Rosa Mae, Larry Gale / Mary Loue Williams / Gracie Glassman; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Ruby, my dear, Thelonious Monk / Fred Bouchard (lyrics); Lyric sheet (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Ruby, my dear, Thelonious Monk / Sally Swisher (lyrics); Lyric sheet (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Run run run, Parts (guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #186 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Run to love, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Sad Sunny, Christine Gardner; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/13)